immap.org 2006-10-19

# View Privacy

**Privacy Policy for the Vietnam Veterans of America Foundation's (VVAF)**

At Vietnam Veterans of America Foundation (VVAF), we value your support and we are committed to protecting your privacy. Our site is a safe environment for anyone who visits or makes a donation. The purpose of this statement is to share with you our policy concerning your privacy. 

  * Who are we?
  * What information do we collect and how do we use it?
  * Do we share your information?
  * Do you use cookies?
  * How do we provide a secure environment for online transactions?
  * How do you contact us regarding your information?
  * Can I use photos from your website?

Vietnam Veterans of America Foundation (VVAF), a non-profit, charitable, 501(c)(3) organization, is an international humanitarian organization that addresses the causes, conduct and consequences of war through programs of advocacy and service for victims of conflict around the world. 

**What information do we collect and how do we use it? **

When you visit our site, we collect some non-identifying basic information. This includes total number of visitors, pages viewed, and other non-identifying information. We use this aggregate information to improve our site and to make your experience on our Web site as smooth as possible. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. 

Donations and purchases made online to us are secure. Donations and purchases are made through VVAF's third-party partners - VeriSign. 

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). All of this information is collected on a voluntary basis. We use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our organization. The user's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may always opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected via the screensaver survey at our site. We use this aggregate data to understand our Web audience's overall demographics and tailor our content, services and programs accordingly. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to: [development@vi.org](mailto:development@vi.org)
  2. You can send mail to the following postal address:  
Vietnam Veterans of America Foundation (VVAF)  
1725 Eye Street, NW, Fourth Floor  
Washington, DC 20006  

 **Correct/Update**

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. You can send email to: [development@vi.org](mailto:development@vi.org)
  2. Send mail to the following postal address:  
Vietnam Veterans of America Foundation (VVAF)  
1025 Vermont Ave, NW, Seventh Floor  
Washington, DC 20005  

VVAF and its partners never send unsolicited e-mail to donors. If you have subscribed to an e-mail newsletter and wish to be removed from the list, email: [development@vi.org](mailto:development@vi.org) and request to unsubscribe from any list. You may also correct or change your contact information via the same process. 

**Do we share your information?**

All functions for which VVAF uses your contact information are clearly spelled out. For instance, we use visitor contact information from the registration form to send users -- at their request - information about VVAF programs, research and updates. If you choose to receive newsletters by e-mail, you may opt-out of receiving future mailings at any time; see the unsubscribe section below. 

We do not share your personal information with any third party. It is our policy not to sell, trade, or rent your personal information to anyone. We reserve the right to change our policy at any time. If we choose to change our policy, you will be given the option to remove your name from our database. 

We do not share your information with telemarketing centers. Your phone number is used only to contact you if we need to verify order information and occasionally to thank you for your contribution. 

We may disclose to third parties aggregate statistics regarding donations but these statistics do not include any personally identifying information. The information given includes: total number of donors, total amount of donations for specific periods of time, and referring Web sites. Aggregate information of this kind is used to encourage fundraising partnerships. 

We use third parties to process our credit card transactions. They receive the credit card number and other personal information of our donors/users only to verify credit card numbers and to process credit card transactions in a secure environment. 

**Online Security  Information  
**VVAF's online donations are handled by VeriSign, a leading company designed to operate and protect billions of interactions across the world’s voice and data networks. VeriSign does not store, sell, rent, or share your information with any other entity besides the designated charity, VVAF. Click here for VeriSign's [privacy policy.](http://www.verisign.com/Privacy/index.html)  

Purchasing Products: Amazon Affiliate Program  
VVAF is also an affiliate partner with Amazon.com to sell books and music. Click here for Amazon's [privacy policy:](http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/subst/misc/policy/privacy.html/002-7751737-6153820)

Amazon.com does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. They may choose to do so in the future with trustworthy third parties, but you can tell Amazon not to by sending a blank e-mail message to [never@amazon.com](mailto:never@amazon.com). (If you use more than one e-mail address to shop with Amazon, send this message from each e-mail account you use.) 

**Other Sites  
** This site contains links to other sites. VVAF and [http://www.vvaf.org](http://www.vvaf.org/) are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Do you use cookies?**

A "cookie" is a small piece of information that is sent by a Web server to be stored on a Web browser, so that it can later be read back from that browser the next time this unique visitor returns to that Web server. This becomes useful for having the browser remember specific information about this visitor like location of their last visit, time spent, or user preferences. The cookie is a text file that is saved in the browser's directory and is stored in RAM while the browser is running. Also, the cookie may be stored on the computer's hard drive once you log off from that Web site or Web server. 

Currently, the VVAF site does not use cookies. In the future, we may use cookies to provide customized content for individual users and monitor the effectiveness of certain online campaigns. 

**How do we provide a secure environment for online transactions?**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. PayPal conducts online transactions using SSL, the leading industry protocol that provides security for transferring credit card numbers and other personal information over the Internet. The secure environment is indicated on the browser with the display of a lock or key on the browser status bar. The display of the secure icon indicates that encryption has been activated. 

**Can I use photos from your website?**

The use of our photos is prohibited. If you would like to use a photo for personal use, please contact us at [webmaster@vi.org](mailto:webmaster@vi.org). If you would like to purchase a reprint of any photos, please contact Alexis Fermanis at [afermanis@vi.org](mailto:afermanis@vi.org)

**How do you contact us regarding your information?**

You can send anonymous donations simply by sending a money order to us at the address found at the bottom of this privacy statement. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: 

Vietnam Veterans of America Foundation (VVAF)  
1025 Vermont Ave, NW, Seventh Floor  
Washington, DC 20005  
Phone: 202-483-9222  
Facsimile: 202-483-9312
